[Music]
hello guys this is your coach Dan your
financial advisor and before we start
let me just say thank you again to
everyone who subscribed to my channel I
really really do appreciate it if you
are new here and you haven't subscribed
the atleast click on the subscribe
button and also the notification bells
so you will be notified whenever I post
videos on financial planning and
managing your personal finances so today
simply lon Papa hip-hop Ilan company
enroll in Sun Life policy not in sub epi
online and also how to make the payments
ah hi so if you're ready let's begin so
to start let's go to BPI not combat th
log into our account and then for this
tutorial I'm actually using an iPad with
a safari browser so hi Lanka mobile
device Ingram is mo but make sure it's a
desktop version after logging in to your
account click on other services and then
manage recipients on the upper right
side click on add new recipients and
then choose builders under recipient for
the biller just look for Sun Life of
Canada Philippines or type in Sun Life
of Canada Philippines now it's time for
you to type in your policy number under
the reference number section so the
policy number normally starts with 0 8
for vul policies 0 5 for traditional
policies once you're done click Next and
confirm the information you just put in
you will get a notification saying
papadelis ability I know six digit code
so wait for the six digit code via SMS
and then type it in the six digit code
number and then click on submit
it normally takes just a few seconds so
just be patient and wait for the SMS and
then once you're done you should get
confirmation that the enrollment was
successful now that should done in
enrolling your account you can now
proceed to make your first payment so
click on payment and then choose the
bank account where the fund is going to
be coming from and then type in the
amount you're going to be paying you can
also make changes to the frequency of
payments as well as leave a note for
this transaction and there you go you
can now make your payments online using
VP ice website or you can download the
BPI mobile app and make your payments
there if you find this video useful
please click the like button leave me a
comment and subscribe to my channel
thank you and see you again
[Music]